Guide to the William T. Cannady Architectural Projects Records, 1956-2018 MS 577
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Addendum I, 170081
  - Undergraduate and Graduate work, 1956-1962; 170480
    - Harvard. Graduate work-dormitory complex for MacAlestor College, 1961-62; 172308 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Harvard. Graduate work-World's Fair Pavilion, 1961-62; 172309 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Harvard. Graduate work-House for Radcliffe College, 1962; 172311 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence files, resumes, firm portfolios, 170559
    - Correspondence file, May 1991; August-December 1992; 172339 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence file, January-July 2001; 172340 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence file, January-June 1993; 172342 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence file, July-December 1993; 172341 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence file, January-August 1994; 172343 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence file, September-December 1994; 172344 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Resumes, 1960, 1962; 172346 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Caudill Rowlett Scott - photographs, drawings, n.d.; 172347 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - William T. Cannady & Associates - Firm resume and selected projects (2 folders), 172349 (Box 16, Folder 9-10)
    - William T. Cannady & Associates - selected projects, 172350 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - William T. Cannady & Associates - Firm resume and bank projects, 172352 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Cannady, Jackson, & Ryan - Firm resume, 172353 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Willis, Bricker & Cannady - Portfolio, 172354 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Willis, Bricker & Cannady - resume, ca. 2001; 172356 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Projects, 170558
    - Goleman and Rolfe - Houston Intercontinental Airport, schematic designs, 1963-64; 172358 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - William T. Cannady & Associates - 7803 Forest Condominiums, 172396 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - William T. Cannady & Associates - Cannady House III, 1991; 172367 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Conference center in Japan, 1991; 172370 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - William T. Cannady & Associates - Addition to the Gymnasium, Rice University, 172374 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - William T. Cannady & Associates - Cannady House IV (2401 Nottingham) (2 folders), 1996; 172409 (Box 16, Folder 21-22)
    - Willis, Bricker & Cannady - Houston Downtown Management District. Transit superstop Feasibility study, 1996; 172376 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Willis, Bricker & Cannady - Independent Living Center, Sealy, Texas, 1997; 172378 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Willis, Bricker & Cannady - Palisades, 1997-99; 172380 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Willis, Bricker & Cannady - Towne Place Plaza, July 1998; 172381 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Bricker & Cannady Architects - Lochinvar Golf Club, 2000; 172382 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Bricker & Cannady Architects - Avondale House, Feasibility study for new building, 2001; 172383 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Bricker & Cannady Architects - Higher Education Portfolio presented to Rice University, n.d.; 172410 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Belmont Village, Hollywood, California, 2001; 172384 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Bricker & Cannady Architects - Master plan for parks, recreation and open space, Harris County, Texas, May 2001; 172388 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - 2323 Shakespeare, built 1974, 172362 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - McLean House, Ft. Worth, Texas, 2001; 172390 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - 9005 [Kellr] promotional materials, n.d.; 172398 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Kirby Shopping Center, n.d.; 172404 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Tatlici Villa, n.d.; 172405 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Texas A&M parking canopies, n.d.; 172406 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Webb Residence, n.d.; 172407 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - William T. Cannady - Miscellaneous drawings and renderings, ca. 1960s; 172359 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Conceptual planning work, n.d.; 172408 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Articles, 170560
    - Newsclippings, 1961, 1966; 172412 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Texas Architect, February 1962; 172411 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Article on Cannady I house [unknown Japanese publication], 1972; 172413 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Architectural Record, Record Houses of 1981, 172414 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Harvard Magazine, January-February 1992; 172415 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Southern Living, vol. 33, no. 3, March 1998; 172416 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Healing, Memorial Hermann Healthcare System, Winter 1998; 172417 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Perspective, a publication of American Institute of Architects/Houston, March 1998; 172418 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Architecture, April 1999; 172419 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Perspective/Houston, May/June 1999; 172420 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Texas Architect, May/June 1999; 172421 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Perspective, A publication of the American Institute of Architects, Houston, July/August 1999; 172422 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Architecture, September 1999; 172423 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Architectural Record, September 1999; 172424 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Perspective, A publication of the American Institute of Architects, Houston Chapter, September/October 1999; 172425 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Houston Chronicle Magazine, December 12, 1999; 172426 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - AIArchitect, vol. 7, January 2000; 172427 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Perspective, A publication of the American Institute of Architects, Houston Chapter, January/February 2000; 172428 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Perspective, A publication of the American Institute of Architects, Houston Chapter, March/April 2000; 172429 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Checkset, Newsletter of the Texas Society of Architects, April 2000; 172430 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - E.E. Reed Construction, April 2000; 172431 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Properties: a Celebration of Excellence from Martha Turner Properties, June 1999; 172432 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Snapshot: current Houston Design on View, 172433 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Office & Commercial real estate, Summer 2001; 172434 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Houston Lifestyles & Homes, September 2001; 172435 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Working: Design and Research, Rice School of Architecture, 2001-02; 172436 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Texas Architect, January/February 2002; 172437 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Perspective, A publication of the Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, March/April 2002; 172438 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Perspective, A publication of the Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, May/June 2002; 172439 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Architecture, July 2002; 172440 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Perspective, A publication of the Houston Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, July/August 2002; 172441 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Sallyport, Spring 2003; 172442 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Texas Architect, September/October 2004; 172443 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Rice Design Alliance - Houses on the bayou map, 2006; 172444 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Houston Chronicle, March 2, 2008; 172445 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Rice: magazine for Rice University, no. 1, 2008; 172446 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Cite, Fall 2010; 172447 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Houston Chronicle, November 18-24, 2010; 172448 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Houston Chronicle, February 17-23, 2011; 172449 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Journal of Architectural Education, October 2011; 172450 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Texas Architect, January/February 2012; 172451 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Texas Architect, vol. 62, no. 05, September/October 2012; 172452 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Pinnacle, Houston Real Estate, n.d.; 172453 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Southampton: a walking tour (Cannady designed houses on pg. 7, 11, 15), n.d.; 172454 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Rice School of Architecture - The things they've done, n.d.; 172455 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Four Houses book project, 1997-98; 172456 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Four Houses book project, 2000-02; 172457 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Awards, Personal, 172458
    - 46th annual P/A awards - Jones plaza renovation, 1999; 172459 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - 47th annual P/A award submission - Houston Urban Parks, 1999; 172460 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - 47th annual P/A award submission - University of Houston Downtown, 1999; 172461 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Shaping Texas - Texas Society of Architects, October 21-23, 1999; 172462 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Designing Excellence for the new century, 1999-2000; 172463 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Celebrate Architecture - University of Houston Downtown, April 14, 2000; 172464 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - AIA Houston - University of Houston Downtown, 2000; 172465 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - The Park People - Preservation Award, Westside High School, 2001; 172466 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Rice University - service awards, February 2, 2005; 172467 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Urban Land Institute - certificate, 2001; 172468 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - AIA Houston certificate of membership, 2008; 172469 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - George W. Bush Inauguration commemorative invitation, 2001; 172470 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Photographs, 1988; 172472 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Photograph: Anderson Todd, Ray Brochstein, William T. Cannady, 172473 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Bulletin Board, 2005; 172478 (Box 17, Folder 62)
- Series VI: Oversize Architectural drawings and renderings, 147567
  - Texas A&M University undergraduate work, 1956-1960; 162875
    - First year drawing class - life drawing (2 boards), 1956-57; 162906 (Drawer 157, Item 1-2)
    - Train station - first year (2 boards), n.d., 162907 (Drawer 157, Item 3-4)
    - First year short project - Housing unit for husband and wife (2 boards), 1956-57; 162908 (Drawer 157, Item 5-6)
    - Second year drawing, 1957; 162909 (Drawer 157, Item 7)
    - Tennis Center, second year (6 boards), 162910 (Drawer 157, Item 8-13)
    - Tile competition board, second year, 1958; 162911 (Drawer 157, Item 14)
    - Second year drawing class - Trees used in Architecture, 162912 (Drawer 157, Item 15)
    - Display panel for museum (2 boards), 1957-58; 162913 (Drawer 157, Item 16)
    - Chapel project, second year (2 boards), 1958-59; 162914 (Drawer 157, Item 17)
    - Third year project - A park pavilion, O. Jack Mitchell professor (3 boards), 1958; 162915 (Drawer 157, Item 18-20)
    - Third year sketch problem - A meditation chapel, 1958; 162916 (Drawer 157, Item 21)
    - Fourth year sketch project - A small animal hospital for Bryan, Texas, 1959; 162917 (Drawer 157, Item 22)
    - Fine Arts Museum (4 boards), 1958-59; 162918 (Drawer 157, Item 23-26)
    - Fourth year project - Oceanography Building (7 boards, 1 paper), 1959-60; 162919 (Drawer 157, Item 27-34)
    - Apartment building. O. Jack Mitchell, professor (5 boards), 1958; 162920 (Drawer 157, Item 35-39)
    - 20footcube House project. Cover page. n.d., 162921 (Drawer 157, Item 40)
    - Drawing trees. Purely representational. n.d., 162922 (Drawer 157, Item 41)
  - Projects, 1965-2011; 162923
    - St. Barnabas Episcopal Church, 1965; 147632 (Drawer 158, Item 1-30)
    - Faculty Housing, College of Petroleum and Minerals, Dhahran, Saudi Arabia, 1966; 147631 (Drawer 158, Item 31-47)
    - David Crane House, 1971; 147630 (Drawer 158, Item 48-55)
    - Cannady House, 1972; 147629 (Drawer 158, Item 56-105)
    - Brochstein House, 1972; 147628 (Drawer 158, Item 105-255)
    - Large Axonometrics (Housing, Churches, etc.), 147627 (Drawer 158, Item 256-268)
    - The Commons, 1972; 147626 (Drawer 158, Item 269-284)
    - Brochstein House, 1972-73; 147625 (Drawer 158, Item 285-294)
    - Dunstan Townhomes, 1972; 147624 (Drawer 158, Item 295-306)
    - WTC Ranch, 1974; 147623 (Drawer 158, Item 307-315)
    - Burger Palace, 1973; 147622 (Drawer 158, Item 316-322)
    - Cohen House, 1974; 147621 (Drawer 158, Item 323-326)
    - Children's Mental Health Clinic, 1974; 147620 (Drawer 158, Item 327-334)
    - Brochstein House, 1974; 147619 (Drawer 158, Item 335-339)
    - Steel St. Townhouses, 1974; 147618 (Drawer 158, Item 340-344)
    - Walker's Mark Townhouses, 1974; 147617 (Drawer 159, Item 1-40)
    - Walker's Mark Townhouses, contd., 1974; 147616 (Drawer 159, Item 41-100)
    - Walker's Mark Townhouses, contd., 1974; 147615 (Drawer 159, Item 101-137)
    - Abu Dhabi Hotel, 1974; 147614 (Drawer 159, Item 138-149)
    - Baker, Will Rice, Hanszen College Renovations, 1975; 147613 (Drawer 159, Item 150-186)
    - Sid Richardson/Amigos de America, 1975; 147612 (Drawer 159, Item 187-190)
    - Burger Palace, 1975; 147611 (Drawer 159, Item 191-201)
    - Piney Oaks, 1975; 147610 (Drawer 159, Item 202-208)
    - Cohen House, 1975-76; 147609 (Drawer 160, Item 1-17)
    - Eastwood Public Park, 1976; 147608 (Drawer 160, Item 18-19)
    - Lovett Square, 1977; 147607 (Drawer 160, Item 20-55)
    - Lovett Square, contd., 1977; 147606 (Drawer 160, Item 56-160)
    - Sunset Terrace, 1978; 147605 (Drawer 160, Item 161-171)
    - Hecht House, 1979; Blacke House, 1983, 147604 (Drawer 160, Item 172-180)
    - Christ the King Episcopal Church, Friendswood, TX, 1980; 147603 (Drawer 160, Item 200-206)
    - Blake House, 1984; 147602 (Drawer 160, Item 207-224)
    - TX Dept. of Corrections Training Academy, 1982; Hines Housing Co. Baldwin Swauare, 1978, 147601 (Drawer 160, Item 225-231)
    - Sid Richardson Institute for Preventive Medicine, 1980; 147600 (Drawer 161, Item 1-4)
    - Riedel House, 1981; 147599 (Drawer 161, Item 5-12)
    - Port Arthur Cultural Arts Center, 1981; 147598 (Drawer 161, Item 13-36)
    - Four Townhouses (David A. Todd), Nantucket Dr., 1981; 147597 (Drawer 161, Item 37-53)
    - Church of the Good Shepherd, Tomball, TX, 1981; 147596 (Drawer 161, Item 54-70)
    - Fayette County Savings and Loan, 1982; 147595 (Drawer 161, Item 96-130)
    - Church of the Good Shepherd, contd., 1983; 147594 (Drawer 161, Item 152-170)
    - Ben Franklin Savings Bank, 1982; 147593 (Drawer 161, Item 171-180)
    - Village Square I (Rice Professor Office Bldg.), 1983; 147592 (Drawer 162, Item 1-28)
    - Village Square I, contd., 1983; 147591 (Drawer 162, Item 29-51)
    - Cannady House II, c. 1983; 147590 (Drawer 162, Item 52-64)
    - Schulte House, 1986; 147589 (Drawer 162, Item 65-91)
    - Kempner Residence, 1987; 147588 (Drawer 162, Item 92-105)
    - David Taylor Classics Car Museum, 1988; 147587 (Drawer 162, Item 106-119)
    - Blake House, 1989; 147586 (Drawer 162, Item 120-130)
    - Cannady House III, 1990; 147585 (Drawer 162, Item 131-145)
    - Cannady House III, cont'd, 1990; 147584 (Drawer 162, Item 146-183)
    - Cannady House III, cont'd, 1990; 147583 (Drawer 162, Item 184-207)
    - Tatlici House, Istanbul, Turkey, 1990; 147582 (Drawer 162, Item 208-227)
    - Northern Trust Bank, 1992; 147581 (Drawer 162, Item 228)
    - World Savings and Loan, 1992; 147580 (Drawer 162, Item 229-236)
    - E.B. Cape Public Works Center, Houston, 1994; 147579 (Drawer 163, Item 1)
    - Cannady House, IV, 1996; 147578 (Drawer 163, Item 2-40)
    - London House, 1997; 147577 (Drawer 163, Item 41-58)
    - McLean-Williams House, Ft. Worth, TX, 1998; 147576 (Drawer 163, Item 59-84)
    - Hightower House, 1999; 147575 (Drawer 163, Item 85-98)
    - Krause House, 2000; 147574 (Drawer 163, Item 99-123)
    - Five Star Ranch, 2001; 147573 (Drawer 163, Item 124-152)
    - Prescott House Remodel, 147572 (Drawer 163, Item 153-164)
    - Slade Residence, 2005; 147571 (Drawer 163, Item 165-188)
    - Hospitality Apts., 2007; 147570 (Drawer 163, Item 189-307)
    - Bricker Residence, 2011; 147569 (Drawer 164, Item 1-34)
    - Christ the King Episcopal Church, undated; 147568 (Drawer 164, Item 35-36)
    - Schulte Ranch, Round Top, TX, Undated; 151683 (Drawer 165, Item 1-7)
    - Addendum, 162927
      - Stanford Plaza, 1987; 151684 (Drawer 165, Item 8-138)
      - Litchfield Park Area, Litchfield, AZ, Undated; 151421 (Drawer 166, Item 1)
      - Rice School of Architecture (RSA) Plans, 1980; 151422 (Drawer 166, Item 2-18)
      - Northern Trust Bank Project - 2 black + white boards, n.d.; 162944 (Drawer 166, Item 19-20)
      - Northern Trust Bank - 7 black and white photographs, 162936 (Drawer 166, Item 21-27)
      - Proposed Rice University Main Street garage - mounted on foamboard, November 2, 2010; 162924 (Drawer 167, Item 1)
      - William T. Cannady & Associates, selected works 1965-1993, black and white, mounted on foamboard, 162925 (Drawer 167, Item 2)
      - Selected built projects 1964-2010, mounted on foamboard, 162926 (Drawer 167, Item 3)
      - Cannady House alternate scheme, 1971; 162928 (Drawer 168, Item 1)
      - House for Robert & Judy Ley Allen, S.D. drawing, 1984; 162930 (Drawer 168, Item 2)
      - Katy National Bank, S.D. perspective, 1985-86; 162929 (Drawer 168, Item 3)
      - Wyndham Garden Hotel Carmel, entry elevation (2 sheets), 1988; 162931 (Drawer 168, Item 4)
      - House for lot X in Shadyside, Houston, Texas, 1989; 162932 (Drawer 168, Item 5)
      - Hunter House (construction set), 1997; 162933 (Drawer 168, Item 6)
      - David & Barbara Gibbs house, 1999; 162934 (Drawer 168, Item 7)
      - Christ the King Episcopal Church, Tomball, Texas, n.d.; 162935 (Drawer 168, Item 8)
      - John Knox Presbyterian Church (5 sheets), n.d.; 162940 (Drawer 168, Item 9)
      - Chocolate Bayou Theater axonometric, n.d.; 162941 (Drawer 168, Item 10)
      - Village Square III axonometric, n.d.; 162942 (Drawer 168, Item 11)
      - Texas Department of Corrections Training Academy axonometric, n.d.; 162943 (Drawer 168, Item 12)
      - R. Webb House, Memorial, n.d.; 162950 (Drawer 168, Item 13)
      - Citizens National Bank, Cameron Texas - perspective, 1960; 162951 (Drawer 168, Item 14)
      - New Building for Port Arthur College (now Lamar University), Port Arthur, Texas - perspective (2 sheets), 1964; 162952 (Drawer 168, Item 15)
      - St. Anthony Catholic Church, Beaumont, Texas - measured field drawing, 1958; 162953 (Drawer 168, Item 16)
      - Goleman and Rolfe, Pierce and Pierce - FAA Building at Houston Intercontinental Airport, 1964; 162954 (Drawer 168, Item 17)
      - Retail center for North Blvd and Kirby Drive, 162955 (Drawer 168, Item 18)
      - Olajuwon House, Sugarland, Texas - Schematic Design Presentation (7 sheets), 162956 (Drawer 168, Item 19)
      - Residence at 2401 Nottingham Ave. Roof Truss Layout, October 1996; 171275 (Drawer 168, Item 20)
      - Texas A&M Freshman Architecture Perspectives, 1956; 171277 (Drawer 168, Item 21)
      - Proposed Main Street Garage, Rice University, November 2, 2010; 171280 (Drawer 168, Item 22)
      - Cohen House Renovation. Issued for Construction, June 3, 2005; 179440 (Drawer 168, Item 23)
      - Dodd residence. 3833 Chevy Chase, Houston, 77019. Issued for Construction, June 22, 2012; 179441 (Drawer 168, Item 24)
      - Northern Bank Trust. 4 sheets, December 15, 1992; 179442 (Drawer 168, Item 25)
      - Schematic Design for New wing for Anderson Hall, Rice University. Sterling & Wilford, Architects, 1979; 179443 (Drawer 168, Item 26)
      - 10 posters from 50th Anniversary party at Rice University, William T. Cannady, 2014; 179444 (Drawer 168, Item 27)
      - Mid-Main Properties 3500 Main St, Houston, TX 77002. Sketches, renderings, floor plans. Project #02.7411.000, 2012-2017; 179445 (Drawer 168, Item 28)
      - Mid-Town Transit-Oriented Development, 2007-05-06 (Drawer 168, Item 29-70)
      - Siff Ranch, Burton Texas (Drawer 168, Item 71)
      - New Canopy for Canopy 2401 Nottingham Rd, Houston, TX 77005, 2010-11-26 (Drawer 168, Item 72-73)
      - Krause House Renovation, 2007-12-09 (Drawer 168, Item 74-89)
      - South Elevation WTCH 2, 1982-12-29 (Drawer 168, Item 90)
- Series VII: Addendum II
  - Projects
    - W.T. Cannady & Associates Architects brochure (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Bricker & Cannady Architects project list, 1974-1996 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - BCA client list, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - "BCA promo", 1990-1996 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - "BCA promo", 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Hermann Professional Building modernization, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Slade house design schemes, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Slade house meeting minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Slade house, River Oaks Property Owners, Inc., 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Slade house-Thomsen Co., 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Slade house invoices, 2003-2006 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - King house, 2003-2007 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Slade house structural engineer & surveyor, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Slade house-Becker architect, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Slade house sketches, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Slade house change orders, 2004-2006 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Slade house payment requests, 2004-2007 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Slade house task list, sketches, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Thomsen house, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Cohen House, Rice, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Hospitality apartments -HRDF housing, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Slade house sketches, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Howrey testimony, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Mid-town transit oriented development, 2006-2008 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - 2100 Bartlett townhouses, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Ferguson residence, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Krause residence renovations, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Mid-town transit oriented development, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Lewis Property Co., 2008 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Slade house, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Mid-town transit oriented development, 2009-2010 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Chouest residence, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Canopy [restaurant] awning, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Bricker house, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Gibbs fireplace, 2011 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Mid-town transit oriented development, 2011-2012 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Dodd house, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Big Indian Mountain Association, Inc. entry court, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Slade clinic, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Mid-Main development, 2013-2014 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Project correspondence (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Publications/publicity/marketing
      - 1960s (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - 1970s (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - 1980s (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - 1990s (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - 2000s (Box 19, Folder 13-14)
      - 4 Houses outlines, drafts, proofs, 1998-2002 (Box 19, Folder 15-16)
      - Willis, Bricker & Cannady Architects (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Wm. T. Cannady & Associates, Inc. (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Awards & honors
      - General (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Series VIII: Addendum III, 1959-2018
  - Announcement for "Four Houses" book signing in "The Bulletin", February 2018 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Article from Architect magazine: "Houston's Post Harvey Reckoning", 2017 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Article from Rice magazine: "Four Houses: Design for Change" by William Cannady, Spring 2018 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Article, draft for Houston Chronicle regarding high-speed train, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Certificate from Senator John Cornyn for a flag flown over the U.S. Capitol in honor of Professor Cannady, 2014 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1969-2018 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Flyer, Rice Design Alliance Centennial Tour, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - News Clippings, 2017-2018 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Prep paperwork for "Four Houses", 2013-2016 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Project Feasibility Analysis, 1995-06-26 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Proposal, Dearwater Design, 2016 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Term paper, Texas A&M: "Structural Techniques of the Italian Renaissance", 1959 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Texas Medical Center, "A 50 Year Master Plan", 1999 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - WTCA Housing Experience, 1970-2011 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Griffin House project, 2015 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Greenway Towers project, 2016 (Box 19, Folder 35)